Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010
  - East Asia: China - Course on Chinese History (1800-1921), 1961-1962, undated; cuid16495 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - East Asia: China - Course on Contemporary China, 1960-1962, undated; cuid16496 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - East Asia: China - Economic and Social Change in Communist China, 1960-1961, undated; cuid16497 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - East Asia: China - Economy, 1960-1961, undated; cuid16498 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - East Asia: China - Fairbank, John K., The U.S. and China (Zinn notes), 1961, undated; cuid16499 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - East Asia: China - Family in China, 1960, undated; cuid16500 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - East Asia: China - "Freedom in Communist China" (selected translations from People's Daily), Aug 1961-Sep 1961; cuid16501 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - East Asia: China - General, 1947-1961, undated; cuid16502 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - East Asia: China - Geography, 1961, undated; cuid16503 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - East Asia: China - Government, Law and the Party, 1959-1962, undated; cuid16504 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - East Asia: China - History, 1961-1962, undated; cuid16505 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - East Asia: China - History (early), undated; cuid16506 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - East Asia: China - History, Modern China (1921-1960), 1961, undated; cuid16507 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - East Asia: China - Ideology, 1960-1964, undated; cuid16508 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - East Asia: China - Internal Conditions, 1956-1966, undated; cuid16509 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - East Asia: China - Kuo, Ping-Chia, China: New Age and New Outlook (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16510 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - East Asia: China - Lifton, Robert Jay, Thought Reform and the Psychology of Totalism (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16511 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - East Asia: China - Literature, 1960-1961, undated; cuid16512 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - East Asia: China - Mandarin Conversation, 1961-1962, undated; cuid16513 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - East Asia: China - Nationalities, 1961, undated; cuid16514 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - East Asia: China - Needham, Joseph (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16515 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - East Asia: China - Reform and Revolution - Sun Yat-Sen, John R. Fairbank and Joseph R. Levinson (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16516 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - East Asia: China - Relationship to the West, 1961, undated; cuid16517 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - East Asia: China - Rise of the Chinese Communist Party, undated; cuid16518 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - East Asia: China - Rostow, Walt, George Cressey and Richard Walker (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16519 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - East Asia: China - Sino-Indian Border War, 1962-1963, undated; cuid16520 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - East Asia: China - Taoism, undated; cuid16521 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - East Asia: China - US Foreign Policy toward China, 1958-1962, undated; cuid16522 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - East Asia: China - US Foreign Policy toward China, 1960-1966, undated; cuid16523 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - East Asia: China - Visitors, 1961-1962, undated; cuid16524 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - East Asia: China - Zinn Book Proposal (China: The Shock of Recognition), 1961; cuid16525 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - East Asia: China - Zinn Course "China: Past and Present", Spring 1962; cuid16526 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - East Asia: China and America - Perceptions, 1961, undated; cuid16527 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - East Asia: China and Japan - History of East Asian Civilization ("Rice Paddies"), 1960-1961; cuid16528 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - East Asia: China and Japan - Pelzel, John C., Values and Social Structure (Zinn notes), [1961]; cuid16529 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - East Asia: General - East and West, Race, 1944-1962, undated; cuid16530 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - East Asia: General - History, 1940s-1950s; cuid16531 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - East Asia: General - Survey, East Asian Civilization, circa 1960-1961; cuid16532 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - East Asia: General - Wittfogel, Karl A., Oriental Despotism (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16533 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - East Asia: Indonesia, 1949-1957, undated; cuid16534 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - East Asia: Japan - History, 1965-1979, undated; cuid16535 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - East Asia: Japan - Student Movement (Includes "AMPO: A Report from the Japanese New Left"), 1969-1970, undated; cuid16536 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - East Asia: Korea, 1946-1967, undated; cuid16537 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - East Asia: Taiwan (Formosa), 1953-1961, undated; cuid16538 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - East Asia: Thailand, 1954-1956; cuid16539 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China Geography, Economy, Culture (I), undated; cuid16540 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - East Aisa: Transparencies - China Geography, Economy, Culture (II), undated; cuid16541 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China History (I), undated; cuid16542 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China History (II), undated; cuid16543 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Chinese Art, Religion, Cities, Maps (I), undated; cuid16544 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Chinese Art, Religion, Cities, Maps (II), undated; cuid16545 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Japan, USSR, undated; cuid16546 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Economics, 1966-1967; cuid16547 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Economics, 1973-1979; cuid16548 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Economics, 1980-Mar 1981; cuid16549 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Economics, Apr 1981-Jan 1982; cuid16550 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Economics, 1982; cuid16551 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Economics, 1983-1986; cuid16552 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Economics, 2007-2009; cuid16553 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, 1974-May 1975; cuid16554 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, Jun 1975-1976, undated; cuid16555 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, undated; cuid16556 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Economics: Economic Justice, 1974, 1985, 1991-2001, undated; cuid16557 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Economics: Economic Statistics, 1975-1980, undated; cuid16558 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Economics: Economics and Intervention, 1976-1985, undated; cuid16559 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Economics: Food, 1971-1976; cuid16560 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Economics: General, 1994-2009, undated; cuid16561 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Economics: Health and Safety, 1975-1979; cuid16562 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Economics: Health and Safety, 1980-1983, 1990-2009, undated; cuid16563 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Economics: History, 2002, undated; cuid16564 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Economics: Massachusetts Budget 1975, Sep 1975-Oct 1975, undated; cuid16565 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Economics: Massachusetts Welfare Crisis, 1975; cuid16566 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1974-1978; cuid16567 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1979; cuid16568 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1980-1983; cuid16569 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy - Oil, Basic Information, undated; cuid16570 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Economics: Publications - "An Inquiry into the Nature and Causes of Inequities in the System of Taxation..." (Massachusetts Public Finance Project), 1973; cuid16571 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Economics: Publications - The Review of Radical Political Economics Vol. 7 No. 4, 1975; cuid16572 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Economics: Publications - Should a City Own a Bank? by Peter Anderson and Carl Kalvelage, 1982; cuid16573 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Economics: Publications - What's Happening to Our Jobs? (Popular Economics Press), 1976; cuid16574 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Economics: Publications - Who Really Rules America? by Richard Pelton, 1970; cuid16575 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Economics: Publications - Why Do We Spend So Much Money? (Popular Economics Press), 1975; cuid16576 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Economics: Taxes, 1975-1977, 1982; cuid16577 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Economics: Utilities, 1973-1976, undated; cuid16578 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Edelman, Marion Wright, 2009; cuid16579 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Ellison, Ella (Zinn article and related material on miscarriage of justice), 1974; cuid16580 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel, 1978-1988, undated; cuid16581 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Engels, Frederick: The Origin of the Family, Private Property and the State (Zinn notes), 1942, undated; cuid16582 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Environment: General, 1975-1978, undated; cuid16583 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Environment: General, 1981, 1983-1988, undated; cuid16584 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Environment: General, 1989-1991, undated; cuid16585 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Environment: General, 1992-1997, undated; cuid16586 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Environment: General, 2002-2004; cuid16587 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1964, 1970-1976; cuid16588 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1977-1978; cuid16589 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1979; cuid16590 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1980; cuid16591 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1981-2002; cuid16592 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, undated; cuid16593 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Information Deception, 1974-1979, 1986-1988; cuid16594 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Lovejoy, Sam, 1974, undated; cuid16595 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Nader's Nuclear Issues by Dr. Ralph E. Lapp, 1975; cuid16596 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - "Report of the International Solidarity Conference for Survival" (Osaka, Japan), 1978; cuid16597 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Seabrook Occupation, 1977; cuid16598 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Silkwood, Karen, 1978, 1981; cuid16599 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "Ethics and Politics, Behavior", 1953, 1966, undated; cuid16600 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - "Ethics and Politics, Behavior", 1961, 1966, undated; cuid16601 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "The Family", 1973-1976, undated; cuid16602 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "Famous Faces - From Nixon to Mao" (transparencies), undated; cuid16603 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1972, 1989, undated; cuid16604 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation Informant Program: [Deposition] of John C. Ryan, 2001; cuid16605 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Films, undated; cuid16606 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Fiore, Patrick: "A People's History..." Images (paintings), 2007; cuid16607 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Policy, 1954-1990; cuid16608 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Policy, 1991-1999; cuid16609 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy, 2000-2003; cuid16610 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy, 2004-2009; cuid16611 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Policy, undated; cuid16612 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Policy: Clinton, 1993-1999, undated; cuid16613 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Policy: Ethics, undated; cuid16614 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Policy: Grenada, undated; cuid16615 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Policy: Public Opinion, 1981-1989, undated; cuid16616 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Policy: Roosevelt, Franklin D., undated; cuid16617 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy: Roosevelt, Theodore and Taft, undated; cuid16618 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1966-1988; cuid16619 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): Correspondence, 1975-1980; cuid16620 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): Government Secrecy (includes court documents from James Lafferty, et al. v. William Rogers, et al.), 1970-1975, undated; cuid16621 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Gender and Security Issues, 2009; cuid16622 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Globalization, 2000-2002; cuid16623 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Goldberg, Harvey, 1987; cuid16624 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Goldman, Emma: [Article] Draft, undated; cuid16625 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Before Beginning of Aerial Bombardment, Aug 1990-Mar 1991; cuid16626 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Bush Arguments for War, cuid16627 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Casualties, cuid16628 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - "Hypocrisy", 1990-1992; cuid16629 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Opinions, cuid16630 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Overview, 1991-1998, undated; cuid16631 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - The Press, cuid16632 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests, cuid16633 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests, 1991-1992, undated; cuid16634 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Zinn Articles, Drafts, Notes, 1991, undated; cuid16635 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1990-1994, 1997-1998, undated; cuid16636 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1998-2000, undated; cuid16637 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis - Correspondence between Zinn and Barney Frank, cuid16638 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, 2001-2008, undated; cuid16639 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Oct 2001-Nov 2001; cuid16640 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Dec 2001-2003, undated; cuid16641 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2002-2003; cuid16642 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2004-2005; cuid16643 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Bombing, Casualties, 2003, undated; cuid16644 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Hypocrisy, 2003-2004, undated; cuid16645 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, 2002-2008, undated; cuid16646 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Anti-War Opinion, 2003-2004; cuid16647 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Casualties, 2003-2006, undated; cuid16648 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, U.S. Handover, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16649 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Lies, 2002-2003, undated; cuid16650 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2002-2003; cuid16651 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16652 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Torture, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16653 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - U.S.-Iraq History, 1999, 2002-2008, undated; cuid16654 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Gulf Wars: Guantanamo, 2004-2009, undated; cuid16655 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: Iraq, 1990-2000, undated; cuid16656 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: "A Threat to Peace" (poster), [2002]; cuid16657 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Haiti, undated; cuid16658 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii, undated; cuid16659 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Health Issues, 1968-2007, undated; cuid16660 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Health Issues: "Consumer Interest and Health Reform: The Logic of Withdrawal from Managed Competition" Presentation by Gordon D. Schiff, M.D., 1994; cuid16661 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Helms, Richard: Perjury Case, 1977; cuid16662 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1996; cuid16663 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1998; cuid16664 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Chained and Unchained", 2006-2007; cuid16665 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Kevin, Monkey Monk and the Atomic Funk", 2006; cuid16666 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "The Phoenix", 1996; cuid16667 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - Rebel Angel or The Confessions of an Angry Nigger!, 1992; cuid16668 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Valley of the Shadows or Diary of Darkness", 1993; cuid16669 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - History, 1954, 1965-1981; cuid16670 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - History, 1969-1994; cuid16671 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - History, 1985-1997; cuid16672 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - History, 1995-2006, undated; cuid16673 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - History, 1998-2003; cuid16674 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - History, 2003-2007; cuid16675 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - History (I), undated; cuid16676 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - History (II), undated; cuid16677 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - History: Alien and Sedition Act (1798), 1967, undated; cuid16678 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - History: American Revolution, 1979, 1992, 2004, undated; cuid16679 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - History: Archives, "Oral History of the American Left" (newsletter), 1979-1980, undated; cuid16680 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - History: Class Conflict - 19th Century, 1979, 1988, undated; cuid16681 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - History: Essays (by Zinn and others), 1975-1982, undated; cuid16682 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - History: Haymarket Riots, 1986, undated; cuid16683 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - History: Manifest Destiny, 1941-2004, undated; cuid16684 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - History: Mexican War, 1979; cuid16685 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - History: The New Deal, 1967-1993, undated; cuid16686 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - History: Notes, 1967-1973, undated; cuid16687 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - History: Philosophy of History, 1988, undated; cuid16688 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - History: Potency, 1975-1979, undated; cuid16689 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - History: Science and History, 1967-1982, undated; cuid16690 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - History: The Sixties, 1979, 1997, 1999, undated; cuid16691 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - History: The Sixties, undated; cuid16692 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - History: Socialist Movements of the Early 20th Century, 1968, 1979-1989, undated; cuid16693 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - History: Truman Administration, 1955-1956, 1964, 1974, undated; cuid16694 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1970-1978; cuid16695 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1975-1978, undated; cuid16696 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - History: U.S. Diplomatic History, 1959, undated; cuid16697 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - History: U.S. History (class), 1956-2001, undated; cuid16698 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - History: U.S. and Latin America, 1979-1986, 2003, undated; cuid16699 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - History: Wilson, Woodrow - Foreign Policy Pre-WWI, undated; cuid16700 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - History: Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1937, 1978, 1995, undated; cuid16701 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - History: World History, undated; cuid16702 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - History: World War I, 1939, 1972, undated; cuid16703 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - History: World War II, 1945-1955, undated; cuid16704 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - History and Science: Objectivity, 1965-1992, undated; cuid16705 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - The Holocaust, 1979-1989, 2003, undated; cuid16706 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - The Holocaust: Notes on Peter Novick's The Holocaust in American Life (1999), undated; cuid16707 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Hope, 1990s; cuid16708 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Hope, 2000; cuid16709 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Hope, 2001; cuid16710 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Hope (includes letter from Patch Adams), Jan 2002-Jul 2002; cuid16711 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Hope, Sep 2002-Dec 2002; cuid16712 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Hope, 2003; cuid16713 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Hope, 2004; cuid16714 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Hope, 2005; cuid16715 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Hope, 2006-2009, undated; cuid16716 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Hope: "The People Speak" Script, Notes, 2009; cuid16717 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1968-1974, undated; cuid16718 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1971-1973, undated; cuid16719 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1975-1976; cuid16720 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues: "The Gordon Empire: A Tenant Research Report", 1975; cuid16721 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Human Nature, 1964-1988; cuid16722 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Human Nature, undated; cuid16723 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Human Nature: Why War? by Albert Einstein and Sigmund Freud (pamphlet), 1933; cuid16724 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights, 1987-1994, undated; cuid16725 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights: USSR, 1965-1980, undated; cuid16726 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Human Rights: Various Eastern European Countries - Czechoslovakia, Poland, Yugoslavia, East Germany, 1964-1974, undated; cuid16727 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Ideology, undated; cuid16728 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Ideology: Education, 1969-1988, undated; cuid16729 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Ideology: Education - Bloom, Allan, 1986-1991, undated; cuid16730 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Ideology: Political Theory, 1959-1987, undated; cuid16731 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ideology: Political Theory (includes course outline and notes), 1976-1989, undated; cuid16732 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ideology: The University, 1966-1984, undated; cuid16733 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Imperialism, 1965-1981, undated; cuid16734 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Imperialism: "The American Empire and the U.S. Economy" Reprint from The Age of Imperialism by Harry Magdoff, 1973; cuid16735 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Imperialism: Economics of Imperialism, 1975-1981, undated; cuid16736 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Imperialism: Exceptionalism, 2008, undated; cuid16737 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Imperialism: Imperial Expansion, 2003; cuid16738 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials, 1962-1977, undated; cuid16739 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials (various articles and essays selected and annotated by Zinn), 1950s, 1960s, 1970s; cuid16740 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Imperialism: Post-World War II, 1975-1979, undated; cuid16741 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Imperialism: Third World (includes lengthy letter from Peace Corps volunteer re: situation in Mali and Ivory Coast), 1974-1980, undated; cuid16742 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - India, 1947-2006, undated; cuid16743 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Indians: The Conquest of America, How the Indian Nations Lost Their Continent by Hans Koning, 1993; cuid16744 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Indians: History, 1989-2009, undated; cuid16745 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Indians: History, Early, 1997, 2000-2005, undated; cuid16746 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Indians: History, Early (research materials - notes, articles), 1976-1978, undated; cuid16747 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Indians: History - Post-Civil War (research materials - notes, articles), 1953, 1977, undated; cuid16748 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Indians: History - Removal (research materials - notes, articles), 1969, 1975, undated; cuid16749 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1954-1976; cuid16750 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1977-1978, undated; cuid16751 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Insurgency (Latin America), 1967, 1968, undated; cuid16752 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2001-2005; cuid16753 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2002-2005, undated; cuid16754 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Irons, Peter, 1971, 1980; cuid16755 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - "Just War" (includes E. Haldeman-Julius Little Blue Book 1547 sent to Zinn by Kurt Vonnegut), 1991, 2008, undated; cuid16756 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Kerry, John, 2004; cuid16757 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1972- Oct 1974; cuid16758 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Kissinger, Henry, Nov 1974-2002, undated; cuid16759 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Kosovo, 1998-2000, undated; cuid16760 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Kropotkin, Peter, 1969, undated; cuid16761 (Box 57, Folder 7)